[KING OF COMEDY]
[Episode 7]
♪ Lost in the crowds, we carry on ♪
Anyway...
as for making movies,
♪ Someone will stay
with you through day and night ♪
you guys...
I'll be the director.
♪ The art of loving and being loved ♪
You be the director?
♪ I'll give my all
to get it right for you ♪
Do you know how to do it?
No.
Then how are you gonna direct?
Aren't you here?
♪ Who would risk it all for you? ♪
♪ Locking all the sorrow deep inside ♪
Am I?
♪ Like a clown who can become ♪
Haven't you always been here?
♪ The superhero who makes you smile ♪
I left for a day.
♪ Oh, time ♪
♪ People who live like clowns ♪
I believe you'll help me.
Let's go!
♪ Have long forgotten the dust
on their sleeves ♪
Oh, right!
♪ With honest hearts,
we make this world more tender ♪
That dog died of old age.
♪ Oh, time ♪
♪ We who were once loved by clowns ♪
Busy?
Junnan.
Noodles are here?
Yeah.
Put them there.
I'm looking for Mr. Gao.
-Mr. Gao.
-Jiaoqi!
Jiaoqi!
-Your noodles are here.
-Mr. Chen.
Eat while it's hot.
How did you sleep last night?
Pretty well.
It's just that the AC
was a bit too strong.
I almost caught a cold.
Then don't turn it on.
Besides,
your vehicle is using our electricity.
That number goes up really fast.
Come on. We're already trying to conserve
as much as we can.
We didn't even dare
to turn on all the lights.
See?
Atmosphere.
It's fine.
The electricity bill isn't much.
I'll reimburse you later.
That's good.
When is later?
Aren't we preparing
to tackle them one by one?
I asked you to prepare
the villager roster.
Did you prepare it?
I did.
I'll give it to you later.
Should we set the AC to heat?
Open the freezer door.
Let the cold and hot air clash.
Stir it up a bit.
Let the air circulate and...
Alright, alright.
I can't see it clearly.
What are you waiting for?
Give me the money for the noodles.
I'll give it to you later.
Okay.
Just kidding. My treat.
Take your time.
That's yours too.
So you two are determined
to make it a sure thing
and shoot this movie, right?
Okay.
Since Zhou Ke
isn't participating in the movie,
how about we just leave first?
Let's give Mr. Zhou some time.
I believe in him.
Right.
We came to talk to you today
because we
have a question to ask you.
After all, in this field, you are
the most professional,
the most influential...
Come on.
And the most authoritative...
Well, I...
One.
We want to know
how much it would cost
to make a movie.
That's hard to say.
It mainly depends
on the cast, crew, and production.
It can cost any amount.
What about a good one?
Like the ones we've participated in...
About 300 million.
What about the ones
you never participated in,
the more ordinary ones?
30 million.
Can we do it with 30,000?
Time to sleep.
We only have 9,000 right now.
Can we do it?
You can't.
Think about
how expensive it is to make a movie.
Lighting, camera, art, makeup, props,
food, drink, and accommodation—
isn't all that going to cost money?
You only have 9,000...
Just 9,000?
Then the labor fee
you promised us before...
No, no, no.
Your share has been set aside.
It's not included in this.
You scared me.
I was... just asking.
Understand.
So now...
as long as we have 30,000,
we can do it, right?
Most likely...
maybe.
Okay!
My brother and I will work hard!
How do you plan to work hard?
We'll crowdfund the movie
by getting the villagers
to invest in it.
We'll promise them a share of the profits!
You ended up on this path anyway.
Crowdfund?
You think you can get the money?
You underestimate us too much.
For this fundraising,
I'll handle Yudan, Shengzai,
Zuxian, Qingxia,
Haonan, Chaowei, and Jiahui.
Yes!
And you will handle Chen Langbiao,
Mr. Chenpi,
Mr. Shark, Ms. Haigou, Mr. Haixing,
Mr. Xianyu, Ms. Zicai, and Sangbiao!
Yes!
Sister,
can you give me two easier ones to handle?
If you can't even
overcome this little difficulty,
how can you be the village chief?
Let's start warming up!
Warm-up complete!
Target: 20,000!
Giddy up!
[Give us some money]
[Please]
[Give us money]
[Yeah]
[Ummmm]
[Please have mercy]
[Give whatever you can]
[Take pity on me]
[Give us some money]
[Even a dime or two is fine]
[Don't go! Give us some more]
[Broadcasting Station]
Villagers, invest in our movie!
Now you can invest in our movie.
Then we can develop
better cultural tourism!
And we can make big money!
Sister.
Brother, how is it going?
And you?
My knees are almost swollen with fluid.
My throat is killing me.
I feel like no one
really believes in
investing in a movie.
Even all my unique skills
failed to impress them.
And today, I even had Ms. Haigou
run over my foot
with her electric scooter for nothing.
-Electric scooter?
-She ran over my foot.
Brother,
have you noticed that
every household
has a new electric scooter outside?
Yeah.
Where did they get them?
Do we have one?
Is that the point?
Let's go.
We need to
go find Mr. Maling now.
He will definitely help us.
Right. Let's go.
Wait for me.
This old man is really weird.
Exactly.
If he doesn't agree to the demolition,
why did he make us
carry the scooter up here?
Seriously.
My back is already bad.
How many scooters did we give out today?
A dozen, I think.
A dozen?
It's you!
Fei!
-So what if it's us?
-Run!
Run? Why should we run?
Wait!
Don't!
-Fei!
-Wait!
Fei! Gao Jiaoqi!
Stop it. I haven't got on the scooter yet!
I knew it was them!
That scooter...
Come on. Let's go find Mr. Maling.
Mr. Maling!
Zhen, Jiahao.
You didn't agree to the demolition,
did you?
Demolition?
Of course I didn't
agree to the demolition.
If they do the demolition,
I won't be able to find the treasure.
That's good.
Great. Well, Mr. Maling,
can we talk about
investing in the movie?
Let's sit down and talk.
Impressive.
Mr. Maling,
your moving castle
has been upgraded again?
Last month,
a motorcade came from Harbin.
I repaired their cars.
One of them
gave me a large sum of money.
I used this money
to upgrade my moving castle.
Now I call it
Harbin's Moving Castle.
That's great.
So do you have money
to invest in our movie?
Of course.
Last month,
a motorcade came from Harbin.
I repaired their cars.
One of them gave me a large sum of money.
I used this money
to transform my moving castle into
Harbin's Moving Castle.
That's great.
Perfect timing.
Are you interested in our new movie?
I put this large sum of money
into my Harbin's Moving Castle.
You used all the money?
As I just said,
a motorcade came from Harbin...
Alright.
Mr. Maling, I get it.
So you have no money now?
I have more and more equipment now.
When I find the treasure,
I can invest a large sum of money in you.
It will be soon.
How long will that take?
Well then, Mr. Maling, get some rest.
We'll go ask others.
Jiahao.
If you have extra dry rations at home,
bring some for me.
I haven't been sleeping well lately.
I'm groggy and hungry.
Then we'll go back
and bring you some fish balls.
Okay.
Zhen, Jiahao.
If you want to make a movie,
I can provide some technical support.
Although we went to so many houses
and didn't raise a single cent,
we did recruit a person.
Let's welcome Mr. Maling to the team.
Let's not be too optimistic right now.
We're literally facing problems
both internally and externally.
I'll make two points.
First,
now, the villagers
don't believe we can make a movie at all,
so they don't dare to invest.
Yes.
Second,
Gao Jiaoqi and Fei
are giving away electric scooters
door to door.
Isn't this just causing trouble for us?
If this continues,
we are done for.
So,
we need to do something big now
to let them know
that we are serious about making a movie.
Otherwise, if we keep waiting,
the villagers will be less likely
to believe us.
Okay.
The key is that we don't have a script.
What are we going to shoot?
It's fine.
It doesn't matter.
We can shoot
some establishing shots first.
What are establishing shots?
As its name implies,
it's a shot with no people,
used to establish the setting—
just the surroundings,
flowers, plants, things like that.
If there are no people,
how can we make it big?
We can make a big scene when we shoot.
Make it look grand and spectacular.
How do we do it?
We can do aerial filming.
Right, we can do aerial filming.
That's a good idea.
What is aerial filming?
Aerial filming
is exactly what it sounds like.
Aviation! Shooting from the sky.
Shooting from the sky?
But we don't have the equipment.
This is my flying fortress.
Can this fly?
How much of a scene can this make?
[Ten Tips for Directors:
1. Stay true to yourself.]
[2. Listen to other people's advice.
3. Don't shoot big scenes! Don't ever do it!]
Ke.
Is this little snowman...
What are you doing?
Writing a diary.
I've known you for over 20 years.
How many words have you written in total?
They are preparing.
Aren't you going?
No.
If you're not going, I'll go.
I have to go.
Then I'm going.
Go ahead.
Are you really not going?
Why would I go?
Then I'll go by myself.
Keep writing.
Do you know how to spell the word "diary?"
D-I-A-R-Y.
Don't go.
This is my flying fortress.
It's made of the chief's security camera,
the chief's clothes,
the chief's curtains,
and the chief's rope.
I affectionately call it
Mr. Hug.
You should call it Mr. Chief.
The monitor connected to it
will transfer the aerial footage
to my phone in real time.
Is it reliable?
Yes.
Six years ago,
I rode it around the world.
Around the world?
You traveled around the world?
It exploded as soon as I left the village.
Isn't that unreliable?
Every time it exploded,
I patched it up.
There isn't a single piece
of the original fabric left.
We can call it the Balloon of Theseus.
Every time it exploded, you patched it up?
How many times have you fallen?
Mr. Maling,
you can actually leave the village by car.
Riding this thing?
It's a miracle you've survived this long.
The unoccupied version is 100% reliable.
It won't get anyone hurt.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Let go.
Go!
-Gosh!
-Theseus!
It was so heavy.
It almost dragged me away.
Mr. Maling,
how do we get this back
after the aerial filming?
We don't.
When it completes the mission
given by humans,
it should go where it wants to go.
Making movies really burns money.
Mr. Zhou would definitely be very happy
if he saw this.
I wonder where he is now.
Help!
Isn't Mr. Zhou right there?
It's getting higher and higher!
Ke!
Mr. Zhou!
-Ke!
-Mr. Zhou!
Ke!
How can you catch up by running?
Mr. Zhou! What should we do?
The flying rescue backpack I designed
can finally come in handy.
Somebody help!
What should we do?
Ke!
-Ke!
-I'm coming.
Zhou Ke!
Ke!
Come down! I'll catch you, Ke!
Mr. Zhou!
Ke!
Oh my!
-Mr. Zhou!
-Ke!
Ke!
My foot hurts!
Mr. Zhou...
Mr. Zhou is in the sky!
Mr. Zhou!
Ke!
Help!
Here! Here!
Mr. Zhou is up there!
Hold on, Ke!
It's getting higher and higher!
[Thirty-Six Stratagems]
[Romance of the Three Kingdoms]
Jiaoqi.
Eat them yourself.
Thank you.
Zhou Ke and the guys are making a movie.
Shouldn't we sabotage it?
Just that Zhou Ke?
How capable can he be?
Can he fly?
Ke!
Don't be afraid!
What should we do?
How...
Use this! Use this!
I got it! I got it!
It's getting higher!
We're doomed.
Won't he fall down?
It's fine.
Below him is the sea.
He won't get hurt.
He can't swim.
Ke!
Mr. Zhou!
We'll save you later!
Zhou Ke?
-Ke! Ke!
-Mr. Zhou!
What should we do?
Mr. Zhou!
Ke.
Give him mouth-to-mouth!
How am I going to explain this to his mom!
Blow harder! Blow harder!
Ke!
Oh my. I'm a bit short of oxygen.
-Let me do it!
-I can't do it anymore!
Come on!
Ke!
♪ The longest dream I've ever had ♪
♪ Is loving you
while hiding it from the world ♪
♪ Sharing this secret only with myself ♪
♪ It's because I'm not smart ♪
♪ And don't know how to deduce ♪
Zhen?
♪ Figuring out the hidden meaning
when it's too late ♪
♪ The longest dream I've ever had ♪
♪ Is searching for you
all over the world ♪
♪ Following closely like the rhythm
of breathing ♪
♪ You are right there ♪
♪ So intimate ♪
♪ Because fate has brought us here ♪
♪ Slowly scattering into the sky ♪
Good. Very good.
You forced me.
[You all must die]
Help!
Help! Help!
Let me out!
Can't you just not work?
Will you support me if I don't?
Okay, I'll support you.
I'll support you
for the rest of your life.
Stop.
Shengzai,
why is Chen Junnan
in your shooting plan?
I'm just trying
to create a horror atmosphere.
I love the suspense dramas on Light On.
If Chen Junnan acts in it,
it would be so perverted.
I don't want to act with him.
So he can't.
I was just giving an example.
If Chen Junnan doesn't work,
Jiahao is fine too.
You also think I have a perverted vibe?
What do you think, Mr. Zhou?
First,
I'm just your consultant.
Why am I in it?
Second, didn't we agree
that Shengzai and Yudan would act?
I can act.
But I don't want to do his script.
I want to act in what I like.
Hey!
What's wrong now?
I'll support you!
Divine Lord.
You finally said it.
Welcome back, Divine Lord!
Welcome back, Divine Lord.
I am Mo Lihong!
I am Mo Lishou!
I am Mo Lihai!
I am Mo Liqing!
Welcome back, Divine Lord!
Welcome back, Divine Lord.
Divine Lord, you finally said it.
Divine Lord?
What's going on?
You are Divine Lord Tianchou from heaven.
I am Fairy Liuxu.
We came down to the mortal world
to undergo a trial.
Only when you say "I'll support you"
can we return to the immortal realm.
It's been nine lifetimes.
You finally said it.
Nine lifetimes?
Stop.
I can't take it anymore.
It's too melodramatic.
What's wrong?
I just like romance dramas on Love On.
You two don't usually
watch the same channel?
We watch TV at different times.
But I like this version.
I want to watch it.
Then I definitely won't act in it.
Suit yourself.
Alright.
Let me share a comedy one.
Hey!
What?
Can't you just not work?
Will you support me if I don't?
I'll support you.
Take care of yourself first.
Idiot.
Cut!
Where did you find this actor?
He won't die
even after being shot so many times.
Come on.
My acting philosophy
might be completely different from y—
I designed my act. I...
Juan, your meal is here.
Hello, hello.
Excuse me, is there a box lunch for me?
Are you kidding me?
I've lived for 37 years,
and I've never seen
such an unprofessional actor as you!
Get out of here!
Wait a minute.
Are you 37 years old?
I was born on June 22, 1962.
What's wrong?
Get out of here.
You are a puddle of mud.
Your life is cheaper than an ant's.
[Profile: Du Juan]
[Liu Piaopiao]
[Yin Tinchiu]
Where am I?
Mr. Chen Jiahao,
born on June 22, 1962,
suffers from
severe dissociative identity disorder.
We will now perform a lobotomy on you.
No!
I'm not sick! I'm not sick!
Don't go! Don't go!
I don't have
dissociative identity disorder!
We don't have
I don't have
dissociative identity disorder!
Excuse me.
What does this have to do with comedy?
Humor. Dark humor.
It's quite dark,
but...
Let me tell you
an original story
I've kept hidden for a long time.
[Work Hard]
I think it's pretty good.
Me too.
I also think it's very good.
I think it's excellent!
It's excellent!
Mr. Zhou, what do you think?
I think... What's our budget?
9,527.
That should be enough for half the movie.
Mr. Zhou, when you make a movie,
why do you always need so much money?
Well, his plan requires special effects
from start to finish.
I just...
It's hard to shoot.
We can agree to the demolition.
When the demolition funds come down,
we'll have money to make the movie.
Are you crazy?
We want to make the movie just because
we don't want the demolition.
Jiahao, go to town with me tomorrow
to get some Chinese medicine.
I won't take it.
I just couldn't figure it out
for a moment.
Alright.
The first script meeting
for "King of Comedy"
is adjourned!
Bye. I need to sell seafood.
Ms. Zhen.
You... you don't need to...
be too anxious.
I'll figure something out for the script.
As for the money,
we'll just take our time.
-Zhen.
-Zhen, you're back?
Zhen is here!
Zhen is back!
Zhen! You're back?
Don't scam people again.
Yeah.
You scared me to death.
Zhen,
when you asked us to invest before,
none of us did.
On one hand,
there was a mysterious force
stopping us.
On the other hand,
we didn't know
if your project would succeed.
Zhen.
Mr. Sangbiao, I'm Jiahao!
It's okay.
I know your concerns.
I don't blame you.
I saw Mr. Zhou
hanging on the hot air balloon,
risking his life.
The last time I saw someone work so hard
was Jackie Chao.
I love Jackie Chao.
I love Jett Li!
Mr. Zhou.
Even someone who isn't from our village
worked so hard.
How can we, the villagers here,
not support you
and just stand by
doing nothing?
-Right!
After discussion,
we unanimously decided
to support you!
Thank you all!
Thank you so much
for believing in me
and our team.
I will remember every penny you invested.
We are all investors of this movie.
I will not let you down.
When our village gets better,
we will invest together,
make money together,
and share the dividends together!
Zhen!
What's wrong, Jiahui?
Are we here for dividends?
We watched you grow up!
This is our token of appreciation!
Just consider it our support for you!
We don't want dividends!
Write it down!
Come here, everyone!
Here, here!
Don't push! Don't push!
Line up! Line up!
How much?
How is it?
I lost count again.
How many times have you counted?
Okay, okay, stop counting.
It's 4,056 in total.
2,000 in cash,
200 in daily necessities,
and an IOU for 1,856.
So... are we still making the movie?
Yes. We must.
This money is the villagers' trust in us.
We must make the village better.
We can't let them down.
Right!
I totally understand how you feel.
You are very excited, right?
You could say
you're the hope of the whole village.
But the problem now
is right in front of us.
We have no script,
no money,
and no dire—
You could count as a director,
but you haven't shot anything before.
You have no experience, so...
How do we do this?
Don't worry, Sister.
Well...
How about we shoot
with whatever money we have?
We have 2,000,
so let's do it with 2,000 for now!
Worse comes to worst,
I'll shoot it.
I just don't know
if I can handle it.
I'll learn it now.
Sister, don't be like this.
If you are like this...
I...
At worst, we'll let the villagers down
and get kicked out!
We are orphans anyway.
As long as we are together,
anywhere is home,
right?
Can I say a few words?
To be honest,
if we want to make a long movie now,
it might not be realistic.
But don't worry.
I still think we can do it.
If we can't make a long movie,
let's make a short one.
It's not meant to be a movie
released in theaters anyway.
Isn't the point
to make the village well-known?
First, money.
I don't think it's a problem.
We can do it
according to how much money we have.
We didn't spend any money
on the things we made before.
We'll use our villagers as actors
and local materials for scenes and props.
We don't have equipment,
so let's shoot with our phones.
Maybe it has an unexpected effect.
Did I say these things
here before?
It doesn't matter.
Second, the script.
The scripts we talked about today
were indeed a bit bold.
It's okay.
I'll help you with it.
I'll take care of it.
Third...
Speaking of the director...
It was indeed partly my fault before.
But later on, this situation...
And Zhen...
doesn't know...
I'll be the director!
Let's hurry up and finish the script
and start shooting immediately.
Is it too late?
Yeah!
Mr. Zhou, I knew you could do it!
Very good!
Great! Great!
How about this?
Let's cook a meal!
Okay.
Let's take it as our kick-off banquet!
Okay!
I'll cook myself!
I'll help you!
Ms. Zhen, well...
So it's not too late for me to come back
and be the director now?
♪ Lost in the crowds, we carry on ♪
Of course.
In that case,
♪ Someone will stay
with you through day and night ♪
will I get paid?
Of course. Don't worry.
Your money is not in that 9,000.
♪ The art of loving and being loved ♪
I've already set it aside for you.
What I mean is...
♪ I'll give my all
to get it right for you ♪
I have a little idea.
Since funds are so tight right now,
♪ Who would risk it all for you? ♪
how about...
I put my money into this?
♪ Locking all the sorrow deep inside ♪
No!
♪ Like a clown who can become ♪
You already agreed to be our director.
We can't take your money.
It's fine. Aren't we short of money now?
♪ The superhero who makes you smile ♪
You can give it to me later
when you have it.
Will your sister agree?
♪ Oh, time ♪
My sister...
Dinner is ready!
♪ People who live like clowns ♪
Let's not tell her.
Use it secretly first.
♪ Have long forgotten the dust
on their sleeves ♪
No need.
I've made up my mind.
I appreciate your kindness.
Thank you.
♪ With honest hearts,
we make this world more tender ♪
Don't thank me.
I should be thanking you.
If you hadn't saved me,
I would have flown over there by now.
♪ Oh, time ♪
Why are you being so polite?
♪ We who were once loved by clowns ♪
If you hadn't been
on that hot air balloon,
the villagers
wouldn't have trusted us so much.
♪ Can become superheroes too ♪
See? That...
♪ Saving every inch of sorrow ♪
Zuxian.
She doesn't love Jackie Chao anymore.
She loves you now.
Anyway,
no matter what,
♪ Then the world is whole again ♪
thank you for saving me.
And thank you for being the director.
You're welcome.
Then let's eat.
Okay.
Let's go.
Come on.
Come on!
The oil is about ready, right?
-It's ready!
-Put it in!
Director Zhou, you've started working?
Why didn't you make a sound
when you came over?
I'm a doer. What's wrong?
Didn't you say you wouldn't make movies
or direct anymore?
Didn't your reverse psychology
get to me?
You could tell?
You were colluding with them.
If Zhen hadn't said
she'd make me boiled shrimp...
You did this for boiled shrimp?
Mainly to give you a way out.
You were hesitating,
wanting to participate
but embarrassed to say it.
Did you think I couldn't tell?
Go away.
Thank you then.
You're welcome.
-Are you...
-No.
You didn't even know
what I was going to ask,
and you said no.
You gave yourself away.
You were acting guilty.
And you were accusing others
to cover yourself.
Since ancient times,
no one has ever been able
to resist a beautiful woman.
I have to say,
Zhen is indeed quite cute.
Her face, I...
Don't talk nonsense.
Is this the reason?
Is it because of this?
Then why?
You're looking down on me. You know?
I had to step up,
both emotionally and logically.
Okay, then tell me.
Emotionally speaking?
Emotionally speaking...
In the village,
my reputation is so good now.
Talking nonsense, huh?
Look at how much the villagers trust me.
It was so touching.
Would I still be human if I didn't do it?
Logically speaking?
Logically speaking,
they need to make a movie now.
And we happen to know how.
As for yourself?
I've been bursting with a sense of justice
since I was a kid.
As for me?
It can make money.
That's true.
Then as for Zhen?
As for Zhen...
It's still because of Zhen, right?
She's part of the reason, of course.
They offered us money.
And they don't know how to direct.
It's not easy for them.
Most importantly, she saved my life.
That was so brave of her. Otherwise...
And the mouth-to-mouth...
So many people were watching.
Do you like Zhen?
Stop it!
Keep your voice down!
You always talk nonsense!
What if she hears you?
I don't like her!
-You don't like her?
-I don't like her.
Really?
No, I don't like her. I don't like her.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's very simple.
I like her, okay?
I want her to be my sister-in-law.
I want her to be my brother's wife.
Stay out of it.
I'll go ask her.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
I'm asking, not you.
I need to ask if she has a boyfriend.
Otherwise, you won't have a chance later.
Right?
I don't plan to be her boyfriend. You...
Remember.
I am the number one Casanova in Shudian.
Just rest assured.
-I'm going!
-Don't be too...
Don't, don't, don't!
Don't ask her too directly!
Please bless me.
Please let it work.
Bless me!
Mouth-to-mouth?
You went too far!